[
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 4x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 4/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 17x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 8x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 6x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 2x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 2x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 15x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 15/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 6x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 2x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x dx",
    "answer": "-15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 10x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 3x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 3x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 18x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "6x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "13/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 2x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 16x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 16/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 3x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "11/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 7x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 8x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 8/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 2x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 11x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 9x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 8x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 8/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "4x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 2x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 12x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 2/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 + 11x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 + 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 10x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 3x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 4x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 4/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 7x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 4x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 6x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 9x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 4x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 - 11x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 - 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 7x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -19x dx",
    "answer": "-19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 5x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 7x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 10x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 6x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 19x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 19/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 9x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 3x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 3x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 2x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 14x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 7/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 3x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-18/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 9x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 7x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 3x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 10x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-15/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 5x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 3x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 1/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 9x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 8x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 8/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 10x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 10/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x dx",
    "answer": "6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 3x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-16/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 19x^3 dx",
    "answer": "19/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 16x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 16/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 5x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 12x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 5x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 7x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 7/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 6x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 9x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 6x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 2x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "16/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 2x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^3 dx",
    "answer": "11/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 2/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 11x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 11/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 10x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 10/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 8x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 7x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 7/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-16/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 7x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 8x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 8/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 2x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 8x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x dx",
    "answer": "-9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 2x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 3x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 7x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 7/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 14x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 7x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "16/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 9x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x dx",
    "answer": "13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 5x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-17/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 6x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 2x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 19x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "19/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 4x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 7x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 7/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 4x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^4 dx",
    "answer": "12/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 10/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 9x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 7x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 6x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 7x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 6x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 2x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 8x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 8/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "14/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 16x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 16/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 6x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 2x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 7x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 7x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 7/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 5x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 10x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x dx",
    "answer": "-17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-16/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 3x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 7x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 9x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-15/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 6x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 3x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 5x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 2x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "16/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 18x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "18/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 4x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 2x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 2/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 9x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 8x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "11/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 6x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 8x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 8/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 3x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 3x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 2x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 3x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 6x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-17/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-18/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 6x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 3x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 15x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 15/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 8x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 9x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^3 dx",
    "answer": "15/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 20x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 10x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x dx",
    "answer": "-8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x dx",
    "answer": "-8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 4x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 13x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 3x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "11/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "17/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 8x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "5x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 2x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 19x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 19/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 2x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "12/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 5x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 1/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 9x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 10/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 15x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 5x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 8x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 3x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 4x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 4/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 4x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 5x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 3x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 8x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 5x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 5/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 8x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 8/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 11x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 13x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 4x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 4/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 9x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 5x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 7x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 10x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 10/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 1/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 10x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 10/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 7x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 18x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 5x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 3x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 6x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 2x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 10x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 10/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "14/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 18x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "13/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 4x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 2x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 1/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 3x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 7x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 7/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 6x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 5x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x dx",
    "answer": "-15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 19x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "17/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 2x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 8x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 3x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 9x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^4 dx",
    "answer": "12/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 9x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x dx",
    "answer": "-6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 5x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 3x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "11/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 15x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 17x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 4x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 4x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 4/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 1/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 9x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 5x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 3x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 4x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 4/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-13/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 8x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 4x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 4x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 10x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 6x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 2x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x dx",
    "answer": "8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 5x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 12x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 4x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 4x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 7x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 7/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x dx",
    "answer": "13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^4 dx",
    "answer": "17/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 9x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 2x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 2/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 8x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 8/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 5x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-15/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-18/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 2x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "13/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 18x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 10x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 7x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 7/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 9x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 2x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 7x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 10x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 10/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 16x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 16/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 6x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 5x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-17/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 9x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 18x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 3x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 3x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 4x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 8x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 12x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 10x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 10/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 8x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 2x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 5x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 3x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 7x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 7/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 10x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 2x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 4x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 16x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -19x dx",
    "answer": "-19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 13x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 5x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 3x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 8x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-15/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 2x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 5x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 1/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 13x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 13/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 9x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 2x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 9x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 8x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 8/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 4x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 3x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 + 15x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 + 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-17/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^2 dx",
    "answer": "16/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-11/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 14x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 7x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 2x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 2x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 7x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 7/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 8x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 8/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 6x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 2x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 2x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 7x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 7/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 10x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 4x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 4/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 9x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 7x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 10x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 10/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 18x^4 dx",
    "answer": "18/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-17/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "16/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 18x dx",
    "answer": "9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x dx",
    "answer": "6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 11x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 10x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 10/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 8x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 8/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 6x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 3x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 14x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 7x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 8x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 8/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 6x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 2x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 2x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 10x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 - 11x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 - 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 6x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 2x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 2x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 2/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 9x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 2x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 3x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 7x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -20x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 9x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 4x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 4/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "11/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "5x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 3x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 6x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 2x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^4 dx",
    "answer": "11/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 5x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 4x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 9x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 9x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "17/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 1/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 5x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 3x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -22x dx",
    "answer": "-11x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 5x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 5x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 15x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 10x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 7x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 6x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 2x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 2x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 6x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 3/2x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 3x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 1/4x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 6x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 2x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 5x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 + 15x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 + 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 12x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "13/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-16/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 7x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 18x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 9/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 10/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 7x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 17x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 8x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 8/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 14x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 7/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 19x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "11/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 5x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 5/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 11x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 11/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 8x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 8/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 7x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 5x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 5x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 6x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3/2x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 5x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 2x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 7x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 7/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 3x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 9x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -19x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-19/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 5x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 5/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 + 8x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 + 8/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 1/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 3x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 3x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 5x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 5/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 8x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 1/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 10x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x dx",
    "answer": "-17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 2x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-11/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 9x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 4x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 7x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 8x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 5x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x dx",
    "answer": "6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 5x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "17/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 6x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 5x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x dx",
    "answer": "-7x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 5x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 5x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 7x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 7/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^4 dx",
    "answer": "11/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 3x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-17/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-16/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 16x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 3x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 19x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 9x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 8x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 2x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 7x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 7/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^4 dx",
    "answer": "16/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^2 dx",
    "answer": "17/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 8x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 8/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 10x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 18x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 9/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 5x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 2x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 2/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 8x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 7x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 7/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 3x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 4x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 2x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 2/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 10x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 4x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 8x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 11x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 11/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 9x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^4 dx",
    "answer": "17/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 19x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 19/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 3x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 16x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "12/5x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 7x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 7/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 2x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 2x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 3x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 19x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "19/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 5x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 15x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 10x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 10/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 10x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 10/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 8x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 7x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 8x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x dx",
    "answer": "11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 9x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 7x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 7/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 1/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 7x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 8x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 10x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 6x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 10x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 6x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 2x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 12x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "12/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-12/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 5x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-13/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 2x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 2/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 2x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 1/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 16x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 6x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 8x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 8/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 2x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 12x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 13x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 5x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 5/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-13/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 13x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + 15x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 15/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 2x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 8x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 8/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 4x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-13/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 + 11x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 + 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 3x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 10x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 10/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 6x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 5x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 10x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 9x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 9x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 7x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 7x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 2x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 4x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 4/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 8x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 2x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 2x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 1/2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 8x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 8/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - 15x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 15/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 9x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 8x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 10x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 19x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 19/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 8x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 10x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 10/3x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 7x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 7/3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -15x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 10x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 + x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 10x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 7x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 - 2x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 - 1/2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 3x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 16x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "16/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 10x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 13x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + 4x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-5/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - x^2 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x dx",
    "answer": "3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 8x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "17/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 7x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 7/4x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "-x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x dx",
    "answer": "13/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 + 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 + 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 10x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 8x^3 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 2x^4 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -13x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-13/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 + x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 + 1/3x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 9x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 9/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 - 10x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5 - 10/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 + 5x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 - 3x^3 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 17x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 17/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 10x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 5/2x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 8x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 8/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 3x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 3/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 8x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 8/3x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -17x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-17/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x dx",
    "answer": "2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 4x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 + 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 + 1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 + x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 6x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 2x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -19x dx",
    "answer": "-19/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 - x^3 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 17x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "17/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x dx",
    "answer": "-9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 13x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "13/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-7/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "14/5x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - 4x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -11x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-11/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 + 3x^2 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 + x^3 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^4 - 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 0 dx",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 - 11x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3 - 11/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -16x dx",
    "answer": "-8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-3/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x dx",
    "answer": "-x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 - 6x^2 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 - 2x^3 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^4 + 6x^3 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "3/5x^5 + 3/2x^4 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 4x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 4/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-14/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 6x^2 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + 2x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^4 - 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "11/5x^5 - 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 11x^2 dx",
    "answer": "11/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 + x^3 + 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5 + 1/4x^4 + 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -12x dx",
    "answer": "-6x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "7/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 6x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 3/2x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 - 6x^3 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5 - 3/2x^4 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^2 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "3x^3 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 dx",
    "answer": "x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^4 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/5x^5 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -18x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-18/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 17x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 17/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 8x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 2x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 + 6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 + 3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 - 3x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5 - 3/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x dx",
    "answer": "4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 - 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 - 7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 + 4x^2 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 + 4/3x^3 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 5x^3 - 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 - 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 - 18x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^4 - 6x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 + 7x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4 + 7/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 - x^3 + x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 - 1/4x^4 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 + x dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5 + 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^2 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "2x^3 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 9x^3 + 6x dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - 9/4x^4 + 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 + 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 + 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 + x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^4 + 4x^3 + 4x dx",
    "answer": "1/5x^5 + x^4 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^2 dx",
    "answer": "7/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 + 2x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 + 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 + 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 - 3x^2 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 - 10x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 - 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-7/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ x^2 - 2x dx",
    "answer": "1/3x^3 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^2 dx",
    "answer": "10/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^3 + 8x^2 + 7x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^4 + 8/3x^3 + 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^3 - x dx",
    "answer": "5/4x^4 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -3x^3 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "-3/4x^4 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x^4 - 4x^2 - 8x dx",
    "answer": "7/5x^5 - 4/3x^3 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 - x dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^3 - 5x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^4 - 5/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x dx",
    "answer": "x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 18x^3 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "9/2x^4 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 8x^3 dx",
    "answer": "2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 8x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 15x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x dx",
    "answer": "5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x^4 + 2x^3 + 2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2x^5 + 1/2x^4 + 2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -10x dx",
    "answer": "-5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-6/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x^3 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-5/4x^4 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -7x^3 - 4x^2 + 9x dx",
    "answer": "-7/4x^4 - 4/3x^3 + 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^4 dx",
    "answer": "-8/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - 5x^3 + 5x dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 5/4x^4 + 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 5x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - 5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -14x^4 + x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-14/5x^5 + 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^3 - 8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 6x^4 - x^3 dx",
    "answer": "6/5x^5 - 1/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 7x dx",
    "answer": "7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 5x^4 + 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^4 - 10x^3 dx",
    "answer": "-2/5x^5 - 5/2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-9/4x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -20x^4 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "-4x^5 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^4 - x^2 dx",
    "answer": "2x^5 - 1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 4x^4 dx",
    "answer": "4/5x^5"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^4 - 4x^3 - 6x dx",
    "answer": "-4/5x^5 - x^4 - 3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 10x^3 - 16x dx",
    "answer": "5/2x^4 - 8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x dx",
    "answer": "-3x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^4 + 10x^3 + 3x dx",
    "answer": "9/5x^5 + 5/2x^4 + 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 3x^3 + 5x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "3/4x^4 + 5/3x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^4 + 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/5x^5 + 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^4 + 7x^3 - 9x dx",
    "answer": "2/5x^5 + 7/4x^4 - 9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^2 - 3x dx",
    "answer": "-2x^3 - 3/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -5x dx",
    "answer": "-5/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-1/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^3 - 4x dx",
    "answer": "-1/2x^4 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 14x^4 + 5x^3 dx",
    "answer": "14/5x^5 + 5/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -4x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-4/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - 7x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 7/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 - 6x^2 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4 - 2x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 9x^3 dx",
    "answer": "9/4x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -2x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-2/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -6x^3 - x^2 - x dx",
    "answer": "-3/2x^4 - 1/3x^3 - 1/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^2 + 10x dx",
    "answer": "2/3x^3 + 5x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -9x dx",
    "answer": "-9/2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ -8x^2 dx",
    "answer": "-8/3x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "∫ 2x^3 dx",
    "answer": "1/2x^4"
  }
]